George F. Aker Papers
George F. Aker Papers
1957-1985
Aker, George F.
7 linear ft.
Consists primarily of correspondence with some printed material, reflecting this educator’s professional career. The papers are arranged chronologically under the following associations and institutions with which Aker was affiliated: Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. (1957-1975), Canadian Association for Adult Education (1964-1970), Florida Adult Education Association (1958-1970), Florida State University (1958-1985), Illinois Adult Education Association (1950s-1960s), National Association for Public School Adult Education (1963-1970), and National Seminar on Adult Education Research (1961-1968). Correspondents whose letters are of significant depth and/or duration include Félix Adam, Sam Roy Allen, Ray Ast, Roger W. Axford, Edgar J. Boone, Alexander N. Charters, James H. Fling, Andrew Hendrickson, Cyril O. Houle, Joseph L. Jacques, Eugene I. Johnson, J.R. Kidd, Malcolm S. Knowles, Burton W. Kreitlow, Huey B. Long, Robert A. Luke, Howard Y. McClusky, Jules Pagano, Robert E. Sharer, Robert E. Snyder, and Wilson B. Thiede.
149407
Biographical History
George F. Aker was born June 2, 1927, the son of George Mosier and Vera Aker, in Fort Wayne, Indiana. He married Patricia Lou Lawson in 1946 and was the father of four children: Linda Lou, Kathy Ann, Jon Kent, and Susan Nanette. Aker earned a B.S. in 1950 from Purdue University and both an M.S. in 1958 and Ph.D. in 1962 from the University of Wisconsin. He held faculty positions at the universities of Missouri, Wisconsin and Chicago. In 1963 he joined the faculty of the Florida State University at Tallahassee. At the time of his death in 1987 he was a professor of adult education and director of the Division of Educational Management Systems at F.S.U.
An activist in national adult education organizations, Aker was a member of the Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. and its president from 1969-1970. He also served on the board of directors for the National Association of Public School Adult Education from 1963-1970. An author and editor of several books on the field of adult education, including the Handbook of Adult Education (1970), Aker also wrote numerous research papers, journal articles and training guides. George Aker's major professional interests were in the development of graduate study and research programs in adult education, and in psychological research to improve the efficiency of adult learning, especially among the disadvantaged and in third world countries. In addition, Aker pursued an interest in new systems of non-formal education as well as in the coordination of adult education with community services and the development of educational technologies for older persons.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The George F. Aker Papers consist primarily of correspondence with some printed material, reflecting this educator's professional career. The papers are organized under the various associations and institutions with which Aker was affiliated. Arranged alphabetically, they appear as follows.
Adult Education Association of the U.S.A.
Canadian Association for Adult Education
Florida Adult Education Association
Florida State University
Illinois Adult Education Association
National Association for Public School Adult Education
National Seminar on Adult Education Research
Within each division there may be several sub-divisions, which appear alphabetically.
The collection is predominantly correspondence, which has been arranged chronologically within each organizational division. A Selected Index to Correspondence appears at the end of the inventory. This alphabetically arranged index indicates the various sub-divisions under which selected correspondents' letters are located, but does not provide access to other materials within the collection with which these individuals may have been associated. Among those selected for inclusion in the index are: persons important to the field of adult education; students and colleagues of Aker; nationally-recognized political figures; and/or persons whose papers are part of the adult and continuing education collections at Syracuse University. The latter are indicated by an asterisk preceding the name of the individual and include Charters, Alexander N.; Hendrickson, Andrew; Houle, Cyril O,; Jacques, Joseph L.; Kempfer, Homer; Knowles, Malcolm S.; Liveright, A.A.; Sharer, Robert E.; Sheats, Paul H,; and Stensland, Per G.
The Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. files date from 1957-1975. The period between 1969-1970 is particularly well represented, as during this time George Aker was president of AEA-USA. Within this division are the correspondence and printed material of the AEA's commissions, including the Commission of Professors of Adult Education, and various other committees, councils, and sections. Correspondence, chapter outlines and drafts for the Handbook of Adult Education (1970), of which Aker was the editor, are also included.
A file for the Canadian Association for Adult Education dates from 1964-1970. Included is some correspondence, general organizational information, and publication lists as well as background material and minutes of this organization's 1970 annual meeting.
The Florida Adult Education Association file contains correspondence and printed material from 1958-1970. The printed material includes meeting reports and minutes, constitutions, and the 1966-1967 Yearbook and Membership Directory.
The largest division in the collection is for Florida State University, the files of which range from 1958-1985. Incoming and outgoing correspondence is chronologically arranged but not interfiled. In addition to those individuals already mentioned as important to the collection, there are many other colleagues with whom Aker worked daily and whose contributions are noteworthy, some of whose papers are part of the adult and continuing education collections at Syracuse University (the latter are indicated by an asterisk preceding the name of the individual):
Blake, Garth
Fordyce, Phillip
Gant, Jack L.
Goerke, Glenn
Hand, Sam E.
Hardee, Mel
*Ingham, Roy J.
Jahns, Irwin R.
Jensen, Glenn
Kroop, Russell P.
Marshall, J. Stanley
Rasmussen, L. V.
Schroeder, Wayne L.
Stone, Mode L.
In addition, there are files for the Division of Educational Management Systems which Aker directed following the consolidation of the Department for Adult and Continuing Education and other educational departments within the university. The Institute on Education for Older Citizens (co-directed with Andrew Hendrickson) and the National Institute for Resource Development and Utilization in Adult Basic Education - Phase III are also major sub-divisions under Florida State University. Completing these organizational records are site visitation reports for the Career Opportunities Program, conferences and meetings files, newspaper clippings, and an Information File which includes material on adult education grouped by subject.
There is one file for the Illinois Adult Education Association dating from the 1950s-1960s. This file contains a copy of the constitution and bylaws as well as a readings list and speech from the 1963 annual meeting.
The National Association for Public School Adult Education covers the period 1963-1970. It includes files for Aker's tenure as a member of its board of directors and his involvement with the Professional Development Committee. As is true of the collection in general, these files contain mostly correspondence, but there is some printed material, primarily in the form of budgets, minutes and reports.
The National Seminar on Adult Education Research is the final division in the collection. It covers the annual seminar from 1961-1968, with each file devoted to a particular year. Included in the files may be any combination of correspondence and printed material such as reports, rosters and general seminar information.
Arrangement of the Collection
The following is an outline of the arrangement of the collection. A more detailed listing of the collection contents, with specific references to location, appears below.
I. Adult Education Association of the U.S.A.
A. AEA Reporter
B. Budgets
C. Commissions
D. Committees
E. Conferences
F. Constitutions
G. Correspondence - General
H. Councils
I. Handbook of Adult Education
J. Regional Associations
K. Sections
L. Task Force on Common Concerns
II. Canadian Association for Adult Education
III. Florida Adult Education Association
IV. Florida State University
A. Ad Hoc Committee on Promotion and Tenure
B. Career Opportunities Program
C. Competency Based Program of In-Service Teacher Training in Adult Basic Education
D. Conferences
E. Correspondence - Incoming
F. Correspondence - Outgoing
G. Educational Management Systems
H. Information File
I. Institute on Education for Older Citizens
J. Meetings
K. National Institute for Resource Development and Utilization in Adult Basic Education - Phase II
L. Newspaper Clippings
M. Offender Assistance Project of Florida Junior College
N. Technical and Professional Development Institute for Correctional Educators
V. Illinois Adult Education Association
VI. National Association for Public School Adult Education
A. Board of Directors
B. Conferences
C. Professional Development Committee
VII. National Seminar on Adult Education Research
Related Material
The library holds a considerable number of collections related to adult and continuing education. Please refer to for a complete listing.
In particular, see also the following:
Individuals
Alexander N. Charters
Andrew Hendrickson
Cyril O. Houle
Joseph W. Jacques
Malcolm S. Knowles
Alexander A. Liveright
Robert A. Luke
Robert E. Sharer
Paul H. Sheats
Per G. Stensland
Organizations
Adult Education Association of the USA
National Association of Public School Adult Educators
Persons in this collection whose papers are also held by are indicated in the Selected Index to Correspondence by an asterisk.
Subject and Genre Headings
Adult education; Adam, Félix, 1922-; Aker, George F.; Allen, Sam Roy.; Ast, Ray J.; Axford, Roger W.; Boone, Edgar John, 1930-; Charters, Alexander N.; Fling, James H.; Hendrickson, Andrew, b. 1899.; Houle, Cyril Orvin, 1913-; Jacques, Joseph L.; Johnson, Eugene I.; Kidd, J. R. (James Robbins), 1915-1982.; Knowles, Malcolm Shepherd, 1913-; Kreitlow, Burton W.; Long, Huey B.; Luke, Robert A.; McClusky, Howard Yale.; Pagano, Jules.; Sharer, Robert E., 1900-; Snyder, Robert E.; Thiede, Wilson.; Adult Education Association.; Canadian Association for Adult Education.; Florida Adult Education Association.; Florida State University.; Illinois Adult Education Association.; Institute on Education for Older Persons (Florida State University); National Association for Public School Adult Education.; National Seminar on Adult Education Research (U.S.); Adult education -- Research.; Adult education -- United States.; Older people -- Education.; Educators -- United States.; Correspondence.; Educators.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of George F. Aker, 1976-1986
Inventory
- Adult Education Association of the U.S.A.
  - AEA Reporter, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Budgets, 1968-1970 (Box 1)
  - Commissions
    - Adult Basic Education, 1969-1973 (Box 1)
    - Commission of Professors of Adult Education
      - Annual Meetings, 1964-1972; 1975; 10 folders (Box 1)
      - Committee, Reporting, 1959 (Box 1)
      - Committee, Research and Dissemination Assessment, 1970 (Box 1)
      - Correspondence, 1957-1971 (Box 1)
        See also Selected Index to Correspondence.
      - Membership, 1959-1970 (Box 1)
      - Newsletter, 1972; 1975 (Box 1)
      - Objectives and Activities, ca. 1968 (Box 1)
      - Progress Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
      - Skill Bank Summary, 1968 (Box 1)
      - Study of the Career Patterns of Adult Education, circa 1960 (Box 1)
    - Planning Adult Education Learning Systems, Facilities and Environments, 1968-1974 (Box 1)
    - Research, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
  - Committees
    - Action Now, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Committee of Adult Education Organizations, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Committee on Committees, 1968-1970 (Box 1)
    - Executive, 1967-1970 (Box 1)
    - Future Conferences, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
    - Government Relations, 1969-1971 (Box 1)
    - Inter-Association Relations, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Joint AEA-NAPSAE, 1960; 1968-1969 (Box 1)
    - Legislative Policies, 1969-1972 (Box 1)
    - Mainline, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Membership and Field Services, 1967-1970 (Box 1)
    - National Program Resources Center, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
    - Nominations and Elections, 1967-1970 (Box 1)
    - Publications, 1968-1970 (Box 1)
    - Regional Boundaries, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Relationships between AEA and its Affiliates, 1967-1970 (Box 1)
    - Resolutions, 1968-1970 (Box 1)
    - Social Philosophy, 1968-1970 (Box 1)
    - Steering, 1966-1971 (Box 1)
  - Conferences
    - Annual, 1962-1963; 1967-1971; 7 folders (Box 1)
    - Delegate Assembly, 1967; 1968,; 1969 (Box 1)
    - Galaxy Conference, 1970 (Box 1)
    - 1st National Consultation, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Constitutions, 1965-1970 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, general, 1967-1971; 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Councils
    - State Associations, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
    - Urban Affiliates, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Handbook of Adult Education, 1970
    - Chapter Drafts
      - Part I, Chapter 7, "The Educators of Adults" / Cyril Orvin Houle (Box 1)
      - Part III, Chapter 23, "Curriculum and Content" / Roger W. Axford, 1st Copy, 2nd Copy (Box 1)
      - Part III, Chapter 31, "Self-Fulfillment" / Glenn Jensen (Box 1)
      - Part IV, Chapter 29, "Continuing Education in the Professions" / Alexander N. Charters (Box 1)
    - Chapter Titles and Outlines (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 2)
      See also Selected Index to Correspondence
    - Guidelines, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Preface, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Reference materials (Box 2)
  - Regional associations, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Sections
    - Address lists, 1967-1970 (Box 2)
    - Armed Forces Education, 1962; 1969-1970 (Box 2)
    - Community College, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
    - Community Development, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Continuing Education for Women, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Correctional Institutions, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
    - Graduate Student, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
    - Home and Family Life, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Liberal Adult Education, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Mass Media in Adult Education, 1967-1970 (Box 2)
    - Public Affairs Education, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Training and Professional Development, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Task Force on Common Concerns, 1966 (Box 2)
- Canadian Association for Adult Education
  - Miscellaneous, 1964-1967 (Box 2)
- Florida Adult Education Association
  - Miscellaneous, 1958-1970 (Box 2)
- Florida State University
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Promotion and Tenure (Box 2)
  - Career Opportunities Program - Site Visitation Reports
    - Sequatchie County, 1971 (Box 2)
    - South Carolina Commission for Farm Workers, Inc., 1968 (Box 2)
    - Walker County, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Competency Based Program of In-Service Teacher Training in Adult Education, 1972 (Box 2)
  - Conferences
    - Louisiana-Arkansas Bi-State Conference, undated (Box 2)
    - New York Association for Continuing Education, 22nd Annual Conference, 1973 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence
    - Incoming, 1958-1971; 25 folders (Box 2)
    - Incoming, 1972-1974; 17 folders (Box 3)
    - Incoming, 1975-1985; 41 folders (Box 4)
    - Outgoing, 1958-1971; 27 folders (Box 5)
    - Outgoing, 1972-1984; 46 folders (Box 6)
  - Educational Management Systems
    - Advisory Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 6)
    - North American Conference on Adult Education, 1967 (Box 6)
    - Priorities, 1977 (Box 6)
    - Technical Assistance, 1976 (Box 6)
    - University Simon Rodriguez, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Information File
    - Adult Armchair Education Program (Box 7)
    - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. (Box 7)
    - Civic Education (Box 7)
    - Community Services (Box 7)
    - Florida Council on Aging (Box 7)
    - Holt Adult Education Newsletter (Box 7)
    - Liberal Arts Colleges (Box 7)
    - Migration, Resettlement and Adjustment (Box 7)
    - Military (Box 7)
    - National Center for Health Statistics (Box 7)
    - National Community School Education Association (Box 7)
    - New Institutional Arrangements and Organizational Patterns for Continuing Education (Box 7)
    - Pakistan (Box 7)
    - Professional Training (Box 7)
    - Research (Box 7)
    - Resources (Box 7)
    - Rural Education (Box 7)
    - Texas Education Agency (Box 7)
    - Veterans (Box 7)
    - Youth Employment Act (Box 7)
  - Institute on Education for Older Citizens
    - Correspondence, 1968-1974; 7 folders (Box 7)
    - Grant Applications, 1970-1973; 4 folders (Box 7)
    - Papers by Andrew Hendrickson
    - Program Outline, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Reports, 1969; 1972; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Meetings
    - Administrative Council, 1973 (Box 7)
    - Career Education Curriculum Laboratory Advisory Council, 1973 (Box 7)
    - Comptroller's Advisory Group, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Department Faculty, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
    - Division Directors / Program Leaders, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Program Advisory Committee, 1976 (Box 7)
  - National Institute for Resource Development and Utilization in Adult Basic Education - Phase III
    - Application for Grant, 1970 (Box 7)
    - Final Report, ca. 1971 (Box 7)
    - Progress Reports, no. 2-11, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
    - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 7)
  - Offender Assistance Project of Florida Junior College, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Technical and Professional Development Institute for Correctional Educators, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
- Illinois Adult Education Association
  - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1960s (Box 7)
- National Association for Public School Adult Education
  - Board of Directors, 1965; 1967-1970; 5 folders (Box 7)
  - Conferences, Annual, 1963; 1966; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Professional Development Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 7)
- National Seminar on Adult Education Research
  - Annual meetings, 1961-1968; 8 folders (Box 7)
Selected index to correspondence
An asterisk beside a name indicates that also has that person's papers. In each case, the name is given first and then the folder title(s) and dates where their correspondence can be found. For example, the first index item "Abolfotouh, Mahin - Florida State University / Correspondence: 1967 Oct. 19 (box 5)" indicates that correspondence with Mahin Abolfotouh may be found in the Florida State University / Correspondence folder in box 5, under the date of October 19, 1967.
Abolfotouh, Mahin - Florida State University / Correspondence 1967 Oct. 19 (box 5) 1968 Feb. 19 (box 5) 1971 Jan. 15 (box 5) 1974 Jun. 25 (box 3) 1976 Mar. 9 (box 6) 1978 May 23 (box 4) 1978 Jun. 21 (box 6) 1978 Oct. 8 (box 4) 1978 Oct. 23 (box 4) 1983 Nov. 11 (box 4) 1984 Oct. 25 (box 4)
Adam, Félix - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A / Correspondence, general 1969 Dec. 22 (box 1) 1970 Apr. 27 (box 1) 1970 May 7 (box 1) 1978 Oct. 21 (box 1)
Adam, Félix - Florida State University / Correspondence 1969 Jun. 2 (box 2) 1969 May 7 (box 5) 1969 Jun. 18 (box 5) 1969 Oct. 27 (box 5) 1969 Nov. 5 (box 2) 1969 Nov. 13 (box 2) 1970 Jan. 22 (box 2) (2 letters) 1970 Mar. 30 (box 2) 1970 Jun. 17 (box 2) 1970 Jul. 17 (box 5) 1970 Dec. 4 (box 5) 1971 Jan. 12 (box 6) 1971 Feb. 18 (box 2) 1971 Aug. 23 (box 2) 1976 Jun. 9 (box 4) 1976 Jun. 10 (box 6) 1976 Jun. 29 (box 4) 1976 Aug. 9 (box 6) 1976 Aug. 20 (box 4) 1976 Sep. 22 (box 6) 1977 Mar. 22 (box 6) 1977 Apr. 1 (box 4) 1977 Apr. 10 (box 4) 1977 Aug. 16 (box 6) 1977 Sep. 16 (box 4) 1977 Sep. 19 (box 6) 1977 Oct. 15 (box 4) 1977 Oct. 27 (box 6) 1977 Nov. 7 (box 6) 1978 Mar. 30 (box 4) 1978 Feb. 15 (box 6) 1978 Jun. 21 (box 6) 1978 Jul. 10 (box 6) 1982 Nov. 2 (box 6) 1983 Jan. 20 (box 4)
Agnew, Spiro T. - Florida State University / Correspondence 1970 Feb. 19 (box 2)
Allen, Sam Roy - Florida State University / Correspondence 1967 Oct. 3 (box 5) 1968 Jan. 28 (box 2) 1968 Feb. 9 (box 5) 1968 Feb. 16 (box 5) 1968 Feb. 21 (box 2) 1968 Feb. 27 (box 5) 1968 Jul. 18 (box 5) 1969 Apr. 29 (box 2) 1969 May 23 (box 5) 1969 Jun. 13 (box 2) 1969 Jun. 25 (box 5) 1969 Jul. 14 (box 2) 1969 Aug. 6 (box 5) 1970 Jan. 5 (box 5) 1970 Mar. 28 (box 2) 1970 Aug. 5 (box 5) 1970 Oct. 5 (box 2) 1970 Oct. 8 (box 5) 1971 Jan. 15 (box 5) 1974 Apr. 18 (box 3) 1974 Jun. 6 (box 6) 1975 Jan. 13 (box 6) 1975 Feb. 8 (box 4) 1975 Feb. 14 (box 4) (2 letters) 1975 Mar. 25 (box 4) 1975 May 29 (box 4) 1975 Jul. 21 (box 4) 1975 Dec. 21 (box 4) 1976 Jan. 29 (box 4) 1976 Feb. 9 (box 4) 1976 Feb. 22 (box 4) 1976 Mar. 2 (box 6) 1976 Mar. 8 (box 6) 1976 May (box 4) 1977 May 28 (box 4)
Ast, Ray - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Correspondence, general 1968 Jul. 15 (box 1) 1968 Sep. 4 (box 1) 1968 Oct. 17 (box 1) 1969 Sep. 22 (box 1) 1969 Oct. 21 (box 1) 1969 Nov. 3 (box 1) 1970 Feb. 4 (box 1) 1970 Feb. 6 (box 1) 1970 Feb. 17 (box 1) (2 letters) 1970 Feb. 25 (box 1) 1970 Feb. 26 (box 1) (2 letters) 1970 Apr. 13 (box 1) 1970 May 7 (box 1) 1970 Aug. (box 1) 1970 Oct. 13 (box 1) 1971 Mar. 11 (box 1) (2 letters) 1971 Apr. 29 (box 1)
Ast, Ray - Florida State University / Correspondence 1967 Dec. 12 (box 5) 1968 Jan. 15 (box 5) 1968 Jan. 26 (box 2) 1968 Feb. 9 (box 5) 1970 Jun. 30 (box 5) 1970 Sep. 21 (box 2) 1970 Nov. 2 (box 2) 1971 Mar. 9 (box 2) 1971 Mar. 31 (box 2) 1971 Apr. 27 (box 5) 1972 Oct. 10 (box 6) 1972 Nov. 3 (box 3) 1972 Nov. 14 (box 6) 1973 May 22 (box 3) 1978 Aug. 9 (box 4) 1973 Sep. 21 (box 6) 1978 Oct. 6 (box 4) 1979 Feb. 8 (box 4) 1982 Jun. 28 (box 4)
Axford, Roger W. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Correspondence, general 1969 Jul. 30 (box 1) 1969 Sep. 23 (box 1) 1970 Feb. 6 (box 1) 1970 Apr. 1 (box 1) 1970 May 4 (box 1) 1970 May 12 (box 1) 1970 Jul. 8 (box 1) 1970 Jul. 24 (box 1)
Axford, Roger W. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Handbook of Adult Education / Correspondence 1968 Jul. 12 (box 2) 1968 Nov. 4 (box 2) 1968 Dec. 9 (box 2) 1968 Dec. 30 (box 2) 1969 Jan. 25 (box 2) 1969 Feb. 11 (box 2) 1969 Feb. 19 (box 2) 1969 Feb. 27 (box 2) 1969 Oct. 6 (box 2)
Axford, Roger W. - Florida State University / Correspondence 1964 Feb. 5 (box 2) 1965 Mar. 18 (box 2) 1967 Mar. 7 (box 5) 1967 Aug. 31 (box 5) 1968 Jan. 3 (box 5) 1968 Apr. 10 (box 5) 1968 Jun. 20 (box 5) 1968 Jul. 31 (box 2) 1968 Aug. 2 (box 5) 1968 Aug. 5 (box 5) 1969 Aug. 7 (box 5) 1969 Oct. 21 (box 5) 1969 Oct. 30 (box 2) 1969 Oct. 31 (box 5) 1969 Nov. 13 (box 2) 1970 Jul. 14 (box 5) 1972 Feb. 1 (box 3) 1972 Apr. 21 (box 3) 1972 May 15 (box 6) 1972 Nov. 21 (box 3) 1973 Sep. 19 (box 6) 1976 May 25 (box 6) 1976 Jun. 10 (box 4) 1976 Dec. 13 (box 6) 1977 Feb. 9 (box 4) 1977 Feb. 17 (box 6) 1977 Sep. 16 (box 4) 1977 Nov. 14 (box 4) 1980 Nov. 1 (box 4) 1982 Feb. 25 (box 4)
Boone, Edgar J. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Commission of Professors of Adult Education / Correspondence 1969 Mar. 7 (box 1)
Boone, Edgar J. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Correspondence, general 1968 Aug. 5 (box 1) 1970 Jan. 5 (box 1) 1970 Feb. 6 (box 1) 1970 Mar. 3 (box 1) 1970 Oct. 14 (box 1)
Boone, Edgar J. - Florida State University / Correspondence 1967 Jan. 17 (box 5) 1967 May 4 (box 5) 1967 Aug. 31 (box 5) 1967 Sep. 14 (box 5) 1968 Mar. 14 (box 5) 1968 Apr. 10 (box 5) 1968 Aug. 5 (box 5) 1968 Aug. 12 (box 2) 1968 Aug. 21 (box 5) 1968 Sep. 21 (box 2) 1969 Apr. 8 (box 5) 1969 Nov. 18 (box 5) 1970 Aug. (box 5) 1970 Sep. 28 (box 5) 1974 Mar. 14 (box 3) 1974 Apr. 8 (box 6) 1974 Oct. 4 (box 3) 1976 Feb. 20 (box 4) 1977 Jun. 21 (box 4) 1977 Jul. 1 (box 6) 1979 Jun. 6 (box 4) 1979 Jul. 11 (box 4) 1979 Jul. 17 (box 6)